<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>More Practical Traits (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.MorePracticalTraits</packageId>
  <author>BOXrsxx, Vaniat, LingLuo</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/MorePracticalTraits</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/WAEzk68.png[/img]
Update of BOXrsxx, Vaniat, LingLuos mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1568700181

[img]https://i.imgur.com/7Gzt3Rg.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/MorePracticalTraits][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NOW7jU1.png[/img]
[b]This mod was made to commemorate Gaoshi. ( Gaoshi is a character in the game, not a real person. )[/b]

[b]version：1158[/b]

[b]compatibility:1.0, 1.1, Royalty[/b]

[h1]Introduction[/h1]
The mod adds some practical traits to the game. Different colors indicate the strength of the traits.

[list]
[*]gray -- These traits are neutral or negative.
[*]green -- These traits have some gain effects and the strength is comparable to &quot;fast walker&quot;.
[*]blue -- These traits have some good gain effects and the strength is comparable to &quot;hard worker&quot;.
[*]violet -- These traits have some excellent gain effects so that they have a great advantage in a certain field. The strength is comparable to &quot;industrious&quot;.
[*]pink -- Moe traits. These traits have some unique social effects. The strength is comparable to &quot;hard worker&quot;.
[*]light red -- The traits of &quot;Gaoshi&quot;. These traits come from game videos made by an intriguing(irritating...) Chinese anchor. The strength is comparable to &quot;hard worker&quot;.
[*]red -- The advanced traits of &quot;Gaoshi&quot;. These traits come from game videos made by an intriguing(irritating...) Chinese anchor. The strength is comparable to &quot;industrious&quot;.
[*]golden -- Custom traits. These traits make your character unique. You almost only get the traits with &quot;EdB Prepare Carefully&quot;.
[/list]

The strength of the traits is inversely proportional to the rate of occurrence. It means that you will hardly meet a person with golden traits during normal game time.

[h1]Details[/h1]
Raydarken created a spreadsheet with the trait information. 
[url=https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1V5Mpu0uPNNpcQPrTWixXkLSgWYy2m8xhZ-aAV92dIFA/edit#gid=1163954486]More Practical Traits Mod Info (100% complete)[/url]

Thanks to Raydarken for doing the work that should have been done by me.

[h1]About Gaoshi[/h1]
Gaoshi was a veteran in his 60s. His mother Ayi was younger than him because she had been asleep for a while. Gaoshi and mom landed on a rimworld planet with the chairman named Wang Laoju. They built a colony on this planet.
Gaoshi was a trouble in the colony. He often woos young girls in the colonies and fails. People told privately about his trait of Cannibal. On the other hand, Gaoshi was an all-powerful person and the main force of the colony. He was optimistic and he could always get back from his failure. He guarded the colony silently again and again.


The following is an introduction to Gaoshprovided by Ryusa. Thanks.

Gaoshi is one of the pawns named by Laoju Wang, a famous video game streamer in China. He clipped total 10 video about Rimworld playthrough. Following link is the first episode (in Chinese language, of cause. ). 
https://www.bilibili.com/video/av6630152 
At the end of this video set, Gaoshi and his fellows were all dead due to Wang&apos;s poor gameplay management (but I think that&apos;s he pretend to do this for a more dramatic watching experiences for us). 
R.I.P. Gaoshi.

By the way Gaoshi (搞事) in Chinese means (do something that beyond someone&apos;s ablities to) seek death.


[h1]Thanks[/h1]
user19990313,  RicoFox233,  BiscuitMiner

[h1]Update[/h1]
V1.1
· New traits
· Balance of some original MPT traits
· Tips on MPT traits
· Added SEKIRO and KENSHI related chats ( only F.T. pariah and F.T. adviser have this type of chat )

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Rs6T6cr.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>

