<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>More Practical Traits</name>
  <url>
  </url>
  <author>BOXrsxx, Vaniat, LingLuo</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>BOXrsxx.MorePracticalTraits</packageId>
  <description>


Thanks: user19990313, RicoFox233, BiscuitMiner

version：1158

compatibility:1.0, 1.1, Royalty

This mod was made to commemorate Gaoshi.

The mod adds some practical traits to the game. Different colors indicate the strength of the traits.
&lt;color=#DCDCDC&gt;[gray]&lt;/color&gt;: These traits are neutral or negative.
&lt;color=#33ff00&gt;[green]&lt;/color&gt;:These traits have some gain effects and the strength is comparable to "fast walker".
&lt;color=#66ccff&gt;[blue]&lt;/color&gt;:These traits have some good gain effects and the strength is comparable to "hard worker".
&lt;color=#cc33cc&gt;[violet]&lt;/color&gt;:These traits have some excellent gain effects so that they have a great advantage in a certain field. The strength is comparable to "industrious".
&lt;color=#ff99ff&gt;[pink]&lt;/color&gt;:Moe traits.These traits have some unique social effects.The strength is comparable to "hard worker".
&lt;color=#F08080&gt;[light red]&lt;/color&gt;:The traits of "Gaoshi". These traits come from game videos made by an intriguing(irritating...) Chinese anchor. The strength is comparable to "hard worker".
&lt;color=#FF3030&gt;[red]&lt;/color&gt;:The advanced traits of "Gaoshi". These traits come from game videos made by an intriguing(irritating...) Chinese anchor. 
&lt;color=#FFCC66&gt;&lt;b&gt;[golden]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;:Custom traits. These traits make your character unique. You almost only get the traits with "EdB Prepare Carefully".
The strength of the traits is inversely proportional to the rate of occurrence. It means that you will hardly meet a person with golden traits during normal game time.

内容：
增加更多特性
→ 负面特性：灰色。整体为负面效果
→ 基础特性：绿色。效果期望与原版普通正面属性相当（对比参考：疾行者）
→ 进阶特性：蓝色。效果期望介于原版普通和优秀正面属性之间（对比参考：工作勤奋）
→ 专业特性：紫色。效果期望和原版正面优秀属性相当（对比参考：工作狂，极端神经质）
→ 特殊特性：
粉色。萌属性相关特性。以改善人际关系为主，效果期望介于原版普通和优秀正面属性之间
浅红。以营造背景的正常特性。效果期望介于原版普通和优秀正面属性之间
红色。营造背景的强力特性，综合效果和原版正面优秀属性相当
→ 定制特性：金色。营造背景的极佳特性，某领域的极端强化
正常游戏状态下，各特性有相关参数控制出现率，不会出现优秀特性泛滥的情况，可安心使用。



更新内容：
1.1
→ 兼容1.0,1.1，皇权
→ 增加大量新特性
→ 原有特性的平衡性调整
→ 增加皇权DLC的相关特性（可在没有该DLC的情况下正常使用）
→ 增加只狼，Kenshi相关话题

1.0
→ 增加太吾绘卷相关话题
→ 平衡性调整


B19
→ 增加支持英语和繁体中文（感谢user19990313和脆饼提供大力协助）
→ 增加搞事系列相关特性
→ 增加未来科技全系列相关话题
→ 增加部分特性
→ 增加部分特性的社交特效
→ 取消美观度属性
→ 平衡性调整
→ 整合LingLuo的相关特性


B18
→ 平衡性调整
→ 增加部分特性


A17 1.04
1.整合Vaniat的相关特性
2.调整A16和整合特性效果、出现率
3.原A16特性“石工”取消
4.增加部分特性
5.增加显示特效
6.优化兼容性和读取速度


A16
1.原A15特性“友善”,由于原版增加特性，改名为“热情”
2.调整部分A15特性效果和出现率
3.增加部分特性
4.增加定制特性
5.去掉Gaoshi相关特性，增加以其命名的高级特性
</description>
</ModMetaData>